delyver.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions - Delyver

**Your personal information**  

Delyver Retail Network Pvt. Ltd. (henceforth referred to as DRNPL) is the licensed owner of the brand Delyver and the website delyver.com (henceforth referred to as 'our site' or 'the site'). DRNPL respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy succinctly outlines the manner in which your data is collected and used by DRNPL. As a visitor to the site or when you get in touch with our call center, you are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by our site you agree to the collection and use of your data by DRNPL in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

**What information is/may be collected from you?**

As part of the registration process on the site, DRNPL may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: Name including first and last name, email address, mobile phone number and contact details, Postal code, Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address etc.) and information about the pages on the site you visit/access, your clicks on the site, the number of times you access the page and any such browsing information.

**How do we collect the your information?**

DRNPL will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey or any combination thereof. The site may contain links to other Web sites. DRNPL is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which it does not own, manage or control. The site and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to the Site.

**How do we use your information?**  
DRNPL will use your personal information to provide personalized features to you on the Site and to provide for promotional offers to you through the Site and other channels. DRNPL will also provide this information to its business associates and partners to get in touch with you when necessary to provide the services requested by you. DRNPL will use this information to preserve transaction history as governed by existing law or policy. DRNPL may also use contact information internally to direct its efforts for product improvement, to contact you as a survey respondent, to notify you if you win any contest; and to send you promotional materials from its contest sponsors or advertisers. DRNPL will also use this information to serve various promotional and advertising materials to you via display advertisements through the Google Ad network on third party websites. You can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager. Information about Customers on an aggregate (excluding any information that may identify you specifically) covering Customer transaction data and Customer demographic and location data may be provided to partners of DRNPL for the purpose of creating additional features on the website, creating appropriate merchandising or creating new products and services and conducting marketing research and statistical analysis of customer behavior and transactions.

**With whom will your information be shared  
**

DRNPL will not use your information for any financial purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. DRNPL does not rent, sell or share your personal information and will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. In cases where it has your permission to provide products or services you've requested and such information is necessary to provide these products or services the information may be shared with DRNPL’s business associates and partners. DRNPL may, however, share consumer information on an aggregate with its partners or third parties where it deems necessary. In addition, DRNPL may use this information for promotional offers, to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of the site’s terms of use or to defend against legal claims; special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure. 

**How do we safeguard your information?  
**

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control, DRNPL has in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, DRNPL servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and your information is shared with employees and authorized personnel on a need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. Although DRNPL will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that DRNPL will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

**How can you update/correct inaccuracies in your information?  
**

To correct or update the information you have provided, login to our site and change the details as required in 'My Profile' under the 'My Account' tab. In the event of loss of access details you can send an e-mail to: [customercare@delyver.com](mailto:customercare@delyver.com)

**Policy updates  
**

DRNPL reserves the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to the site.
